Guide to the UH Forensics Team Records
University of Houston Libraries
UH Forensics Team Records
1956-1973
2006-002
10.50 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
University of Houston Libraries
The U.H. Forensics Team Records contains newspaper articles, schedules of tournament events, correspondence, tapes, and photographs relating to the U.H. Forensics Team between the years of 1956-1973. Typically the newspaper articles describe the team's performance at various national tournaments.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
University of Houston
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Physical Characteristics or Technical Requirements:
Special Collections owns the physical items in our collections, but copyright normally belongs to the creator of the materials or their heirs. The researcher has full responsibility for determining copyright status, locating copyright holders, and abiding by current copyright laws when publishing or displaying copies of Special Collections material in print or electronic form. For more information, consult the appropriate librarian.
Arrangement of Materials:
The collection is separated by event with the folders placed in ascending order.
Scope and Contents
The U.H. Forensics Team Records contains newspaper articles, schedules of tournament events, correspondence, tapes, and photographs relating to the U.H. Forensics Team between the years of 1956-1973. Typically the newspaper articles describe the team's performance at various national tournaments. During the 1960s, the U.H. Forensics Team was considered as one of the top rated teams in the country, defeating teams like Harvard in 11 debates while only losing to them 4 times. In 1969, the U.H. debate team won 137 of the 159 debates that they participated in with Dr. William English winning coach of the year. Following the 1969 season, Dr. English spoke about team members Mike Miller, a political science junior, and David Seikel, a political science senior, and said that the two held the "best record of any intercollegiate debate team ever." He then added, "There probably never will be a better team."
The U.H. Forensics Team Records arrived at the archives in very good order, which has been maintained where possible. The collection consists mainly of newspaper clippings directly related to the organization and to the debates that it participated in, however there are a small number of photographs, tournament results, and tapes of the National Debate Tournaments from 1956-1966 also found in the collection.
For preservation and access reasons the collection has been re-boxed and re-foldered. New folder titles conform, as closely as possible, to original folder titles, except when the original was obviously incomplete, incorrect, or confusing. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
Detailed List of Contents
- UH - Charts, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- UH - Clippings, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournament Results, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- UH - Tournaments Air Force, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- UH - Baylor, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- UH - Central State, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- UH - Millsaps, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- UH - New Mexico, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- UH - Northwestern, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- UH - Stephen F. Austin, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- UH - Southeastern, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- UH - S.W. Texas, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- UH - T.C.U, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- UH - Brackets, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- UH - Districts, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- UH - Individuals, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- UH - Matrices, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- UH - Schools, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- UH - Squads, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- UH - States, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- UH - Tournaments, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- UH - Clippings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- UH - Photographs, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournament Results, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- UH - Tournaments: Abilene Christian College, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- UH - Air Force, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- UH - Amarillo, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- UH - Arkansas, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- UH - Baylor, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- UH - Bellaire, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- UH - Central State, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- UH - District III, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- UH - East Central, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- UH - Emporia, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- UH - Millsaps, 11965 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- UH - Novice Nationals, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- UH - N.W. Louisiana, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- UH - S.F.A, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- UH - Southeastern, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- UH - Southwestern, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- UH - S.W. Texas, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- UH - T.C.U, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- UH - Wichita, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- UH - Brackets, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- UH - Districts, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- UH - Individuals, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- UH - Matrices, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- UH - Schools, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- UH - Squads, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- UH - Clippings, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournament Results, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- UH - Photographs 1, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- UH - Photographs 2, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- UH - Tournaments: Air Force, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- UH - Baylor, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- UH - Bellaire, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- UH - Bethany, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- UH - Central State, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- UH - District III, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- District III Submissions (Box 2, Folder 8)
- UH - East Central, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- UH - Emporia, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- UH - Georgetown, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- UH - Heart, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- UH - Louisiana Poly, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- UH - Millsaps, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- UH - N.W. Louisiana, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- UH - O.U., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- UH - PKD Regional, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- UH - SFA, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- UH - Southeastern, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- UH - Southern Mississippi, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- UH - T.C.U., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- UH - Texas State, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- UH - Texas Tech, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- UH - Vanderbilt, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- UH - Wichita, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Tape: Alabama, Harvard, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Tape: Howard, Georgetown, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Tape: Northeastern, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Tape: Redlands, USC, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Tape: Wichita, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- UH - Brackets, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- UH - Districts, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- UH - Individuals, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- UH - Matrices, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- UH - Schools, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- UH - Squad, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- UH - Clippings, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournament Results, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- UH - Photographs, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- UH - Tournaments: Air Force, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- UH - Baylor, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- UH - Bellaire, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- UH - Bethany, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- UH - Central State, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- UH - District III, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- UH - East Central, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- UH - Emporia, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- UH - Harding, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- UH - Heart, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- UH - Final Round, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- UH - Louisiana Poly, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- UH - Millsaps, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- UH - N.D.T, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- UH - O.U., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- UH - PKD National, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- UH - SMS, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- UH - Southeastern, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- UH - Southern Miss, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- UH - S.W. Texas, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- UH - T.C.U, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- UH - Texas A&M, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- UH - Texas Southern, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- UH - Texas State, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- UH - Tulane, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- UH - Vanderbilt, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- UH - Wichita, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Tape: Georgia-Wayne, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Tape: Northeastern, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Tape: N.T.S.U, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Tape: T.C.U.-Wayne, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- UH - Annual Report, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- UH - Brackets, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- UH - Districts, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- UH - Individuals, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- UH - Matrices, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- UH - Schools, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- UH - Squad, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- UH - Tournaments, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- UH - Clippings, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournament Results, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- UH - Photographs, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- UH - Tournaments: Air Force, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- UH - Arkansas, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- UH - Baylor, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- UH - Bethany, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- UH - Dartmouth, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- UH - District III, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- District III Submissions, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- UH - East Central, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- UH - Emporia, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- UH - Georgetown, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- UH - Golden West, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- UH - Harvard, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- UH - Heart, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Heart Final Round, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- UH - Houston, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- UH - Houston Local A, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- UH - Houston Local B, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- UH - Hutchinson, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- UH - Louisiana Tech, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- UH - N.D.T, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- UH - Northwestern, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- UH - N.W. Louisiana, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- UH - Ohio State, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- UH - Oklahoma State, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- UH - O.U., 1968 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- UH - PKD Regional, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- UH - Rockhurst, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- UH - San Jacinto, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- UH - SMS, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- UH - Southeastern, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- UH - Stanford, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- UH - TCU, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- UH - Texas Southern, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- UH - Texas State, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- UH - T.O.C, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- UH - Tulane, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- UH - Vanderbilt, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- UH - Wichita, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Tape: Denver, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Tape: Heart of America, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Tape: Loyola, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Tape: Northwestern, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Tape: Oberlin, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- UH - Clippings, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- UH - Photographs 1, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- UH - Photographs 2, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- UH - Photographs 3, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- UH - Annual Report, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- UH - Brackets, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- UH - Matrices, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- UH - Schools, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournaments Results, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournaments Results, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- UH - Invitations, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- UH - Tournaments: Air Force, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- UH - Baylor, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- UH - Blinn, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- UH - LeTourneau, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- UH - Dartmouth, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- UH - Denver, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- UH - District 3, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- UH - Emporia, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- UH - Georgetown, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- UH - Golden West, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- UH - Harvard, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- UH - H.B.C, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- UH - Heart, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- UH - Houston, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- UH - Houston Intrasquad, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- UH - Houston Novice, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- UH - Letourneau, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- UH - Louisiana Poly, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- UH - Midwestern, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- UH - MIT, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- UH - NDT, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- NDT Final Round, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- UH - NIT, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- UH - Northwestern, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- UH - N.W. Louisiana, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- UH - Oklahoma State, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- UH - PKD National, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- UH - Rockhurst, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- UH - San Jacinto, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- UH - S.F.A., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- UH - SMU, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- UH - Southeastern, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- UH - TCU, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- UH - Texas State, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- UH - Texas Tech, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- UH - Tulane, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- UH - UCLA, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- UH - UICC, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Tape: Denver, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Tape: Harvard, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Tape: Harvard, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Tape: Harvard B, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Tape: ACC Loyola, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Tape: MSU Loyola, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Tape: ACC M.I.T, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Tape: Oberlin, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Tape: St. Anselm's, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Tape: T.C.U., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Tape:: Texas Tech ACC, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Tape: U.C.L.A, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- UH - Brackets, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- UH - Individuals, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- UH - Schools, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- UH - Matrices, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- UH - Clippings, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournaments Results, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- UH - Photographs, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- UH - Tournaments: Air Force, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- UH - Baylor, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- UH - Dartmouth, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- UH - District III, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- UH - Emory, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- UH - Emporia, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- UH - Georgetown, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- UH - Golden West, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- UH - Heart, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- UH - Final Round, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- UH - Final Round, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- UH - Letourneau, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- UH - Marietta, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- UH - MIT, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- UH - NDT, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- UH - Northwestern, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- UH - N.W. Louisiana, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- UH - Oklahoma State, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- UH - PKD Regional, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- UH - Rockhurst, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- UH - San Jacinto, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- UH - SFA, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- UH - SMS, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- UH - TCU, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- UH - Texas, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- UH - Texas Novice, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- UH - Texas State, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- UH - Texas Tech, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- UH - Tulane, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- UH - UCLA, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- UH - USC, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- UH - Wichita, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Tape: Georgetown, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Tape: Kansas B, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Tape: Kansas B, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Tape: Loyola, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- UH - Brackets, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- UH - Calendar, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- UH - Individuals, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- UH - Matrices, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- UH - Schools, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- UH - TOC qualifiers, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- UH - Clippings, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournament Results, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- UH - Photographs, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- UH - Tournaments: Air Force, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- UH - Baylor, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- UH - Colorado, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- UH - Dartmouth, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- UH - District 3, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- UH - Emory, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- UH - Emporia, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- UH - Georgetown, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- UH - Golden West, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- UH - Heart, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- UH - Heart Final Round, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- UH - Houston, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- UH - Letourneau, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- UH - Marietta, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- UH - NDT, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- UH - Northwestern, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- UH - Oklahoma State, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- UH - PDK National, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- UH - Rockhurst, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- UH - San Jacinto, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- UH - SMS, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- UH - TCU, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- UH - Texas, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- UH - Texas Novice, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- UH - Texas State, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- UH - Texas Tech, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- UH - UCLA, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- UH - USC, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- UH - Wichita, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- UH - Wyoming, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Tape: U.S.C., 1971 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- UH - Individuals, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- UH - Brackets, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- UH - Matrices, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- UH - Schools, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- UH - Intercollegiate Speech Tournaments Results, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- UH - Photographs, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- UH - Tournaments: Air Force, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- UH - Baylor, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- UH - District 3, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- UH - Emory, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- UH - Emporia, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- UH - Georgetown, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- UH - Golden West, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- UH - Heart, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- UH - Houston, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- UH - Lamar, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- UH - Letourneau, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- UH - NDT, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- UH - Northwestern, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- UH - Oberlin, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- UH - Oklahoma State, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- UH - Pittsburg, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- UH - PKD Regional, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- UH - San Jacinto, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- UH - San Jacinto Novice, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- UH - SFA, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- UH - SMS, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- UH - Southeastern, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- UH - SW Conference, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- UH - TCU, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- UH - Texas, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- UH - Texas Novice, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- UH - Texas State, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- UH - Texas Tech, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- UH - UCLA, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- UH - USC, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- UH - Clippings, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Heart of America, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- UH - Young America Speaks, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- UH - Photographs, 1950's (Box 10, Folder 34)
- West Point, 1958-1965 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Tape: National Debate Tournament, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)